

EDIT LIPCSEI

JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

- in LinkedIn
- ☑ lipcsei.e@gmail.com
- +36 30 5943336
- Github
- Budapest

SUMMARY

Before Green Fox Academy, I worked as a social worker. Recently, I organized the travelling and care services for people with disabilities at an independent association. A friend recommended GFA to me, and I instantly developed a passion for coding. During my time at GFA, I discovered great joy in exploring the complexities of programming languages and creating practical applications.

MOTIVATION

Coding requires a lot of abilities like creativity, logical thinking, problem- solving skills, attention to detail, patience, perseverance, and adaptability. Thats why I instantly developed a passion for coding. This newfound passion hasignited a profound sense of purpose within me, driving my continuous pursuit of learning and growth in the field. The IT industry also offers a compelling combination of flexibility, boundless opportunities.

LANGUAGES

HUNGARIAN Native ENGLISH Professional working proficiency

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

Languages and frameworks: .Net, Javascript, Typescript , Node.js / Express, React, HTML, CSS, Next.js

Technologies: Jira, Git, GitHub, GitLab, MySQL, SQL

PROJECTS

February 2023 - June 2023

FoxShop Project

Green Fox Academy

Building a second-hand marketplace where users can sell and buy used electrical devices and other products that can be put in pre-defined categories.

Developing the application from scratch, within a 5-person development team. The web application offers as additional functions:

- · user registration and log-in
- advertisements placement, browsing and management
- · category based searching
- messaging services between seller and buyer
- frameworks: Next.js for frontend, ASP.Net Core for backend
- database: MySQL
- testing: Jest and xUnit.net
- architectural style: REST API endpoints
- project management: SCRUM methodology(Jira), Git, including the GitHub platform, for collaborative development.

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2023

Support Service Manager

Civil Érték Egyesület

- Coordinating the work assignments and tasks for employees facilitating the enrollment of employees in
- Training programs, identifying their developmental needs and providing opportunities for professional growth
- Preparing documentation for service recipients, and evaluation reports
 2014 -2016

Employment Consulntant

Civil Érték Egyesület

- Providing job, career, job search, and rehabilitation counseling
- Collaborating with local employment officers, clients, training institutions, and employers
- Conducting small-group counseling sessions for clients

EDUCATION

2023 Oct - 2024 Jan

Nix Learning & Development Center

.NET Course

 Studied .NET Platform, Programming Principles: OOP and SOLID, Architechture and Design Patterns, Database and SQL,ORM and EF, ASP.NET MVC and WebAPI

2022 Jun - 2023 Jun

Green Fox Academy

Fullstack Developer

 Studied HTML and CSS, TypeScript, GIT Version Control System, OOP, Vanilla JS Frontend Development, Node.js / Express, MySQL Database

2004 - 2009

Szent István University,

Social Worker, BA degree